<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IDS 702: FALL 2019</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on IDS 702: FALL 2019</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Note: Please check this page frequently for updates and always remember to refresh the page.

 Date Lesson Slides Reading Lab HW Project    WEEK 1        Tue, Aug 27 Introduction to course         PART I: MULTIPLE LINEAR REGRESSION        Thur, Aug 29 Introduction to multiple linear regression         WEEK 2        Tue, Sept 3 Model assessment, diagnostics and validation I        Thur, Sept 5 Model assessment, diagnostics and validation II        Fri, Sept 6 Lab 1: multiple linear regression (beer consumption in sao paulo)         WEEK 3        Tue, Sept 10 Interactions, transformations, and multicollinearity        Thur, Sept 12 Model building and selection         Final project outline         PART II: GENERALIZED LINEAR MODELS         WEEK 4        Tue, Sept 17 Introduction to logistic regression (HW2 DUE!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policies</title>
      <link>/policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/policies/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Students are expected to know all topics covered in the MIDS summer course review and boot camp. These include basic probability (including conditional probability, expectations and common probability distributions), and statistical inference (including hypothesis testing, confidence intervals, linear regression with one predictor, and exploratory data analysis). Students are also expected to be familiar with R/Rstudio. Due to space constraints, the course is open only to students in the MIDS program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>Supplementary Textbooks These textbooks are great resources for some of the topics we will cover. You do not need to buy them, but you may be able to borrow them from Duke library should you need extra reading materials, besides the class slides and main textbooks. I may also select and adapt questions from the books for your homework assignments from time to time, but you will not need access to them when I do so.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>